

Solid professional career in software development on multiple technologies, with experience in the development of services and products in multidisciplinary teams.

Over the past few years, I have taken on leadership roles, managing and guiding teams to success.

My focus is on promoting a collaborative environment, driving creative solutions and ensuring the delivery of high-quality projects.

#### **SKILLS**

- Extensive technical knowledge.
- Mentoring and leadership experience.
- Experience in project management and planning.
- Work with agile methodologies.

#### **LANGUAGES**

- English Intermediate
- Spanish Native

# MARIA FLORENCIA CHIALVO

Software Engineer

Barcelona, Spain

mf.chialvo@gmail.com (+34) 614463468

### **EXPERIENCE**

### Software Engineer Manager PedidosYa | Buenos Aires, Argentina

Jan 2024 - Present

Leadership of the shopping cart and price calculation team. My main responsibilities include planning, coordination and dependency management of our projects. I foster a positive and agile work culture, and I am in charge of developing talent within the team.

# Principal Software Engineer PedidosYa | Buenos Aires, Argentina

Mar 2022 - Dec 2023

Technical leadership in the fintech tribe working with microservices (Kotlin, Go + AWS). Responsible for the design and implementation of maintainable and scalable solutions, coordinating with other teams, and promoting good development practices seeking the best balance to maximize the value delivered.

### Software Engineer Backend PedidosYa | Buenos Aires, Argentina

Jul 2020 - Feb 2022

Analysis and development in the wallet team, implementing solutions in different languages such as Kotlin and Go in a microservices ecosystem.

## Software Engineer Full Stack Almundo | Buenos Aires, Argentina

Nov 2017- Jun 2020

Mar 2014- Oct 2017

Analysis and development, implementing solutions with various backend and frontend technologies such as Java, Rust, NodeJs, Angular and AngularJS for web applications.

# Software Engineer Full Stack BDF Technology Solutions | Buenos Aires, Argentina

Analysis and development, implementing solutions with various backend and frontend technologies such as Java, JavaScript, AngularJS, NodeJS and PrimeFaces for web and desktop applications.

### **EDUCATION**

**Information Systems Engineering**, completed UTN FRBA | Buenos Aires, Argentina

2011 - 2016